Saul E. Fernandez Urdiano

UI/UX Designer

Compton, CA

Work Experience

Self - Freelance Designer

November 2021 - September 2022, Los Angeles

Created Application Interface Designs for Various Markets and Devices. Sold Designs to Health Wellness Website, Navigational Phone app for school bus routes, Video Conferencing WebApp, Personal Navigational Website. Prototyped and designed on figma. Built on Angular.

Aramark - Junior Software Engineer

September 2021 - June 2022, Irvine

Collaborated with developer teams on designing and maintaining POS systems used by companies nationwide. POS systems were mainly written in C++ with occasional Java and Qt GUI.

Panda Express - Web/Visual Designer

February 2019 - September 2021

Worked on a team that created the Panda Express ordering website and the accompanying mobile app. Prototyped and designed with InVision. Developed in Angular.

Background

Human-Computer Interaction Theories, Principles & Research User Interaction Software Design Testing Software Design: Applications/Web Software Testing, Analysis, and Quality Assurance Computer Game Development Information Retrieval Parsing BD & Data Structures Information Visualization/ Color Theory Agile Project Management

Qualities

Team Player, Flexible Schedule, Great Organization, Self Starter, Detail Oriented, Quick Learner, Resourceful, Hardworker.

Education

SEFU9090.GITHUB.IO

SEFERNAN@UCI.EDU

(323) 498-8088

University of California, Irvine - June 2022

Bachelor's of Science in Informatics (Specification in Human-Computer Interactions), Minor in Education Sciences.

Educational Experience

Senior Capstone

January - June 2022

Created a game to educate students on threats facing marine mammals. Built on Android Studio using Java.

Python Tutor

September 2020 - June 2021

Provided tutoring services for students taking first-year python courses. Helped struggling students pass their courses.

Skills

Programming: Python, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, C++, C#, Java, Swift, TypeScript, MySQL, Firebase.

Design: Illustration & UI graphics, User Flows, Concept sketches, Wireframes & mock-ups.

Prototyping: Rapid prototyping using Figma, Adobe Suite & Invision.

Research: Task analysis & persona Hypothesis, A/B Testing & Experiment, Cognitive walkthrough, Usability Tests.

Tools: Git, React, Angular, Ionic, Xcode, Android Studio, Unity.